A Finding Aid to the Foster Brothers Records, 1875-1973, (bulk 1893-1942), in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
Foster Brothers records
1875-1973
bulk 1893-1942
Archives of American Art
Foster Brothers (Boston, Mass.)
AAA.fostbrot
Archival Resource Key
13 Linear feet
The records of Boston picture frame company Foster Brothers measure 13 linear feet and date from 1875-1973 with the bulk of the material falling between 1893 and 1942. Correspondence, stock records, financial records, writings, miscellaneous business records, printed material, scrapbooks, and photographs document the history of this company that operated a factory, retail store, and wholesale and mail order businesses between 1893 and 1942. A small number of family papers are included, with items pre-dating and post-dating the business.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Helen Foster Osborne, daughter of John R. Foster, donated the Foster Brothers records to the Archives in four installments between 1973 and 1976.
Conditions Governing Access note
The collection is open for research. Use requires an appointment.
Biographical/Historical note
Established by Stephen Bartlett Foster (1856-1932) and John Roy Foster (1863-1931), Foster Brothers opened in 1893 at 164 Boylston Street, Boston. By 1896, Foster Brothers had moved to 3 Park Square, just around the corner from its first location. Eventually, the business relocated to 4 Park Square, where it stayed for the remainder of its existence. The original Foster Brothers factory was housed in the old Parkman's Market building on Cambridge Street in Boston. In 1918, the Fosters built a new factory in Arlington, the suburb in which the brothers lived.
Foster Brothers was known for high quality frames that featured expert carving and gilding by fine craftsmen, consistent with the esthetic and philosophy of the Arts and Crafts movement of the time. Their frames that incorporated elements of early Dutch frames especially appealed to Boston School artists such as Edmund Tarbell and William MacGregor Paxton. Custom orders were welcomed from museums, galleries, collectors, and artists. In the 1890s, Foster Brothers operated a small gallery that featured watercolors and sketches by local artists; sporadic exhibitions continued throughout the 1930s. Early business cards and advertisements indicate that the company sold "wedding presents, etchings, engravings, water colors and picture frames." Among its best selling merchandise were mirrors in a wide variety of styles. As early as 1898, Foster Brothers began to copyright and publish reproductions of paintings, drawings, silhouettes, and miniatures. These were framed in sets and sold by Foster Brothers in its retail shop and by mail order; in addition, they were distributed through department stores, furniture stores, gift shops, and interior decorators.
John Roy Foster was in charge of promotion and merchandising, designing the retail line, and managing the company's wholesale and mail order businesses. Stephen Bartlett Foster managed the factory and oversaw all aspects of the manufacturing. Helen J. Foster, John's daughter, studied art at Smith College and by the late 1920s was a successful manager and saleswoman in the retail store. The Depression brought a sharp decline in sales. After the deaths of John and Stephen Foster, Helen and her husband, Shattuck Osborne, owned and managed Foster Brothers for another decade. Although the business closed in 1942, Foster Brothers frames continue to command high prices and are highly prized and sought after today.
Scope and Content Note
The records of the Boston picture frame company Foster Brothers measure 13 linear feet and date from 1875 to 1973 with the bulk of the material falling between 1893 and 1942. Correspondence, stock records, financial records, writings, miscellaneous business records, printed material, scrapbooks, and photographs document the history of the picture frame company that operated a factory, retail store, and wholesale and mail order businesses between 1893 and 1942. A small number of family papers are included, including items from periods when Foster Brothers was not in business. Scattered throughout the collection are small slips of papers with explanatory notes and background information supplied by the donor, Helen Foster Osborne.
Correspondence mostly concerns routine business with suppliers, distributors, and wholesale and retail customers and is relatively sparse for 1897-1941. Foster Brothers' last year in business, 1942, is well documented and includes letters from S. W. Osborne (Margaret Foster's husband) written while traveling to meet with wholesale clients in cities throughout the Northeast and Midwest.
Stock records include stock cards, inventory records and price lists. Also found are a large number of paper stencils that were used to transfer carving designs to frames, and extensive drawings of frames and moldings including finished, colored drawings by master craftsman C. F. Richter.
Financial records consist mainly of routine accounting records, but also include annual financial reports, orders, and sales records. Among the writings and lists are an unsigned article concerning Foster Brothers' craftsmen and their early use of machinery. Notes include material for a history of mirrors by Helen J. Foster, and "The Art of Framing" by John R. Foster.
The majority of printed material relates to advertising and consists of catalogs and brochures about frames, mirrors, and published reproductions. Eight volumes of scrapbooks also contain printed material consisting of advertising, brochures and catalogs, form letters, and reproductions of miniatures and silhouettes published by Foster Brothers.
Family papers consist of a small number of personal papers of the founders, John Roy and Stephen Bartlett Foster, and also of Helen Foster Osborne (John's daughter). They include Foster Oborne's 1973 reminiscence of having her portrait painted by William Paxton in 1923, John R. Foster's personal account book and Foster Osborne's correspondence with Ernest Donnelley concerning the sale of printing plates and dies from the miniature reproduction business.
Photographs are of founders John Roy and Stephen Bartlett Foster, some of their employees, and early pictures of the first Foster Brothers frame factory on Cambridge Street.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged as 9 series:
Missing Title
Series 1: Correspondence, 1897-1942 (Box 1; 1.0 linear feet)
Series 2: Stock Records, 1905-1942 (Boxes 2-6, 11, OVs 23-24, BVs 13-15; 6.2 linear feet)
Series 3: Financial Records, 1892-1959 (Boxes 7-9; BVs 16-19; 3.3 linear feet)
Series 4: Writings and Lists, 1920s-circa 1942 (Box 9; 0.25 linear feet)
Series 5: Miscellaneous Business Records, 1898-1939 (Box 10; 7 folders)
Series 6: Printed Material, 1893-1947 (Box 10, OV 25; 0.25 linear feet)
Series 7: Scrapbooks, 1906-1942 (Boxes 10, 12, BVs 20-22; 1.3 linear feet)
Series 8: Family Papers, 1875-1973 (Box 10; 6 folders
Series 9: Photographs, circa 1880s-1918 (Box 10; 5 folders)
Picture frames and framing; Art -- Economic aspects; Stencils; Photographs; Drawings; Scrapbooks; Picture frame industry -- Massachusetts -- Boston; Works of art; Osborne, Helen Foster; Osborne, S. W.; Richter, C. F.; Foster, John Roy, 1863-1931; Foster, Stephen Bartlett, 1856-1932
- Correspondence, 1897-1942; Series 1; Archival Resource Key; 1 Linear foot (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents note
  Business correspondence with suppliers, distributors, and wholesale and retail customers concerns routine matters and special orders. The correspondence dated 1897-1941 is relatively sparse and primarily concerns copyright of artwork reproduced by Foster Brothers that was sold, framed, in gift shops, department and furniture stores.
  The year 1942, the company's last year in business, is well documented. Of particular interest are letters from S. W. Osborne (Margaret Foster's husband) written while traveling to meet with wholesale clients in cities throughout the Northeast and Midwest.
  Arrangement note
  Chronological correspondence is followed by alphabetically arranged correspondence.
  - Correspondence, 1897-1915; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1916; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1917; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1918-1919; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1920-1921; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1922-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Abbott - Austin-Hastings Co., 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Babcock - Bittinger, 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Boaler Burchell and Dillon - Boyce Studio, 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Brandenburg - Butterfield, 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Cabot - Closson Co., 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Cocks - Cusik Studios, 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Davenport - Drakenfeld Co., 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - E and E Art Shop - Fulda, 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Gamble - Gump's, 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Hagerty - Hurley, 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Ideal Furniture Co. - Jordan, 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Kahn's Art Gallery - Kromhaut, 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Lake - Lyon Furniture Mercantile Agency, 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Macy and Co. - McVicker, 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - M/E Framing Guild - Myers, 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Nature Food Centres - Osborn, 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Osborne, S. W., 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Ozark Arts and Crafts Center - Payne, 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - P P and H Moulding Co. - Putnam, 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Radas - Ryder, 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Sanders Co. - Sebatia Products, 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Shaker Gift Center Inc. - Swartz, 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Taber - Vixsboxse Art Galleries, 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Wadsworth, Howland and Co. - Waverly Fabrics, Inc., 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Webb - Wyman, 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Yale Athletic Association - Yuenger Manufacturing Co., 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Stock Records, 1905-1942; Series 2; Archival Resource Key; 6.2 Linear feet (Boxes 2-6, 11, OVs 23-24, BVs 13-15)
  This series contains stock cards, inventory records, and price lists in addition to blueprints, drawings, and stencils and designs for wood carving.
  Stock cards (mostly 8" x 10" pieces of mat board) describe merchandise produced or sold by Foster Brothers, including frames for pictures and mirrors, candlesticks, glove boxes, moldings, painted glass and stands. Each card contains at least one image (drawing, photograph, or printed reproduction) of the item and its stock or style number, and sometimes notes dimensions and prices. Some loose images are interfiled with the cards.
  A large number of paper stencils that were used to transfer carving designs to frames survive, although many are fragile. Many stencils are annotated with the corresponding stock or style number; other designs for woodcarving are merely drawn on paper. In addition, there are extensive drawings of frames and moldings, loose and in bound volumes, including finished, colored drawings by master craftsman C. F. Richter.
  One volume titled "Cost on Mirrors" (1929) analyzes the amount of time needed to carve, gild, and polish frames, the cost of materials, and prices of frames #1001-1308.
  - Stock Cards, Archival Resource Key (Box 2)
    - Frames #515-4599, undated; Archival Resource Key; 19 Folders (Box 2, Folder 1-19)
    - Frames #4600-5099, undated; Archival Resource Key; 18 Folders (Box 3, Folder 1-18)
    - Frames #5100-6011; unnumbered, undated; Archival Resource Key; 18 Folders (Box 4, Folder 1-18)
    - Candlesticks #1-8, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Glove Boxes #6-9, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Light Bracket; Wall Candelabra #1-2, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Moldings #1w-186w; #1-172; #4533-4966, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 4)
      (see also BV 13)
    - Painted Glass #1-62, undated; Archival Resource Key; 2 Folders (Box 5, Folder 5-6)
    - Pier Mirrors (#P1-P17), undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Stands #1-40; unnumbered, undated; Archival Resource Key; 2 Folders (Box 5, Folder 8-9)
  - Blueprints, Archival Resource Key (Box 5)
    - Mirrors #1004-1167, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Catalog (includes blueprints and printed reproductions) - Mirrors #1053-1143, undated; Archival Resource Key; 1 Volume (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - "Cost on Mirrors", 1929; Archival Resource Key; 1 Volume (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Drawings (hand colored) by C. F. Richter, Archival Resource Key (Box 5)
    (see also BVs 14-15)
    - Cabinets, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Foster Brothers Mirrors in Room Settings (unsigned), undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Inventories, Archival Resource Key (Box 5)
    - Vol. 1:, 1933-1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Vol. 2:, 1939-1941; Archival Resource Key; (loose leaf notebook, disbound) (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Vol. 3:, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous Lists, undated; 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Price Books, Archival Resource Key; (loose leaf notebooks, disbound) (Box 5)
    - Vol. 1: Stands and Frames, 1919-1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Vol. 2: Frames, 1919-1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Vol. 3: Frames, 1923-1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Price Lists, undated; 1929-1942; Archival Resource Key; 2 Folders (Box 5, Folder 22-23)
  - Stencils and Designs for Woodcarving, #100s-#6000s, unnumbered, undated; Archival Resource Key; 34 Folders (Box 6, Folder 1-34)
    see also OVs 23-24, BV 13
  - Stencils and Designs for Woodcarving, unnumbered, undated; Archival Resource Key; 8 Folders (Box 11, Folder 1-8)
  - Stencils and Designs for Woodcarving, (#1000s-2000s, 4000s), undated; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 23)
  - Stencils and Designs for Woodcarving (unnumbered), undated; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 24)
  - Stencils and Designs for Woodcarving (unnumbered), 1905; Archival Resource Key (Box BV 13)
  - Drawings of Moldings, #1-3038, 1905; Archival Resource Key (Box BV 13)
  - Drawings (probably by C. F. Richter), "Sketches" (mirrors and frames), undated; Archival Resource Key (Box BV 14)
  - Drawings (probably by C. F. Richter), "Mirrors and Frames", undated; Archival Resource Key (Box BV 15)
    (see also Box 5, BV 14; includes boxes, stands, letterhead design, printed reproductions; some loose items)
- Financial Records, 1892-1959; Series 3; Archival Resource Key; 3.3 Linear feet (Boxes 7-9; BVs 16-19)
  Financial records consist mainly of accounting records, but also include annual financial reports, orders, and sales records. There are relatively few records before the early 1900s.
  - Accounting Records, Archival Resource Key (Box 7)
    - Account Balances, Wholesale and Retail, 1940-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Accounts Payable, A-Z, 1936-1941; Archival Resource Key; 2 Folders (Box 7, Folder 2-3)
    - Accounts Payable, Summary, 1919-1938; Archival Resource Key; (5" x 8" cards) (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Accounts Receivable, A-Z, 1907-1940; Archival Resource Key; 4 Folders (5" x 8" cards) (Box 7, Folder 5-8)
    - Accounts Receivable, Summary, 1919-1938; Archival Resource Key; (5" x 8" cards) (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Advertising, 1928-1931; Archival Resource Key; (5" x 8" cards) (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Automobile, Reserve for Depreciation, 1931-1937; Archival Resource Key; (5" x 8" cards) (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Balance Sheets, 1919-1930; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Balances, Sundry Credit and Debit, 1931; Archival Resource Key; (5" x 8" cards) (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Bank Deposits, 1919-1939; Archival Resource Key; (5" x 8" cards) (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Cash, 1919-1939; Archival Resource Key; (5" x 8" cards) (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Cash Journal, Vol. 1:, Jan. 11, 1938-Jan. 1, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Cash Journal, Vol. 2:, Jan. 3-Nov. 1, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Cash Journal, Vol. 3:, Nov. 13, 1939-Sept., 21, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Cash Journal, Vol. 4:, Sept. 23, 1940-Sept. 6, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Cash Journal, Vol. 5:, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 20)
      (see: BV 16)
    - Cash Journal, Vol. 6:, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 21)
      (see: BV 17)
    - Cash Journal, Vol. 7:, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 22)
      (see: BV 18)
    - Code Numbers, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Consignments, 1935-1941; Archival Resource Key; 1 Volume (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Expenses, Factory and Store, 1900-1931; Archival Resource Key; (5" x 8" cards) (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Foster, Georgette K., Helen J., John R. and Estate of John R., 1902-1938; Archival Resource Key; (5" x 8") (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Furniture and Fixtures, 1919-1938; Archival Resource Key; (5" x 8" cards) (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - General Ledger, Profit and Loss, 1938; Archival Resource Key; (see: BV 19) (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Insurance, 1937-1938; Archival Resource Key; (5" x 8") (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Interest and Discount, 1919-1939; Archival Resource Key; (5" x 8") (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Inventories, Consigned, Factory, and Store, 1919-1938; Archival Resource Key; (5" x 8" cards) (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Inventories, Factory and Store Equipment, Supplies, Fixtures, 1920; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Investment Account, 1919-1932; Archival Resource Key; (5" x 8" cards) (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Payroll, 1931; Archival Resource Key; (5" x 8" cards) (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Payroll - Factory, Vol. 1:, 1936-1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Payroll - Factory, Vol. 2:, 1937-1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Payroll - Factory, Vol. 3:, 1939-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Profit and Loss, 1919-1939; Archival Resource Key; (5" x 8" cards) (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Sales and Purchases, 1919-1938; Archival Resource Key; (5" x 8" cards) (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Sales and Purchases; Expenses, 1939-1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Taxes, 1925-1931; Archival Resource Key; (5" x 8" cards) (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Annual Financial Reports, 1925-1932; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Annual Financial Reports, 1934-1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Order Books - Retail, Vol. 1:, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Order Books - Retail, Vol. 2:, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Order Books - Retail, Vol. 3:, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Order Books - Wholesale, Vol. 1:, 1937-1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Order Books - Wholesale, Vol. 2:, 1939-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Sales, Vols. 1-3:, 1892-1910; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Sales, Vol. 4:, 1937-1939; Archival Resource Key; (wrapped package) (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Sales, Vol. 5:, 1939-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Sales Records, Jan. 1942-Jan. 1943; Archival Resource Key; 13 Folders (Box 9, Folder 2-14)
  - Sales, Monthly Summaries, 1926-1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Sales, Davidson, C. E., 1938-1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Sales, Wholesale Sales Trips (itineraries, customer lists, expenses, sales), 1930-1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Accounting Records, Cash Journal, Vol. 5, 1959; Archival Resource Key (Box BV 16)
  - Accounting Records, Cash Journal, Vol. 6, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box BV 17)
  - Accounting Records, Cash Journal, Vol. 7, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box BV 18)
  - Accounting Records, General Ledger, Profit and Loss, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box BV 19)
- Writings and Lists, 1920s-circa 1942; Series 4; Archival Resource Key; 0.25 Linear feet (Box 9)
  Writings consist of articles, lists and notes. An unsigned article concerns Foster Brothers' craftsmen and their early use of machinery. Notes include material for a history of mirrors by Helen J. Foster, and "The Art of Framing" by John R. Foster.
  - Articles by Unknown, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Draft of Mirror Brochure (with illustration), undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Lists, Mailing, 1940-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Lists, Store and Factory Locations; Unusual items Framed for Customers by Helen Foster, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Lists, Trade (by city), 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Lists, Retail Customers (Arlington, Belmont, Boston, Brookline, Cambridge, Lexington, Medfords, Worcester), undated; Archival Resource Key; 8 Volumes in 2 folders (Box 9, Folder 23-24)
  - Lists, Wholesale New England Customers or Possible Customers by Helen Foster, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Notebooks, Helen Foster - Business Information, A-Z, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Notebooks, John R. Foster - Notes and Figures; Lists, 1920s-1930s; Archival Resource Key; 2 Volumes disbound (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Notebooks, Margaret J. Melly [Mrs. McLaughlin] (in charge of wholesale orders and advertising) and Helen J. Foster - "Interesting Information of All Kinds", undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Notes, Artist Biographies by Unknown, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Notes, History of Mirrors by Helen J. Foster, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Notes, Miscellaneous and Lists by Helen J. Foster, circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Notes, Picture Frames; "The Art of Framing" by John R. Foster, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Notes, Reproductions Published by Foster Brothers, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Miscellaneous Business Records, 1898-1939; Series 5; Archival Resource Key; 7 Folders (Box 10)
  Included in this series are copyright and trademark information, a building permit, and records relating to an exhibition of etchings by Dorsey Potter Tyson held at Foster Brothers.
  - Building Permit for Arlington, Mass., Factory, 1918; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Census of Manufacturers, 1929-1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Contracts (Telephone and Electric Co.), 1898-1907; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Copyright Registration for Photograph, "Irene" and Print, "Your Picture of Today Will be the Keepsake of Tomorrow", 1898, 1926; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Exhibition of Etchings by Dorsey Potter Tyson, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Insurance, Workmen's Compensation, 1912; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Trademark of Foster Brothers, 1899; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Printed Material, 1893-1947; Series 6; Archival Resource Key; 0.25 Linear feet (Box 10, OV 25)